The letters were wrestling match.
I tried to get rid of them.
After I had removed all the letters, I took boat polishing agent,
antioxidant and plaster machine on it and it ended
with the letters becoming much shiny.
But there were also the other parts of the flat.
So even though I did all the work, there was the same difference
As it was before though everything was shiny and the letters appeared anyway.
So it ended with me buying color and rolling over them only
to get rid of the letters.
But all the boxes have worked?
I had that on one of my movies that I published
So it was one of the switches until the box had been water -filled.
After the rain it ran down after the side and straight down the switch.
Then when I emptied it, it had standing water
throughout the power switch.
So there I found a new compensation and replaced only that dilemma around it.
But it was only a ten minute job so it was no wonder.
When I drove down this fall, I drove south all the time
And then I had the sun low standing so I was dazzled all the time.
So I got less on it and put silver tape there
To get sunscreen.
I forgot about it so I had it during the entire period in Portugal.
So now I don't get the paste away, it sits in the Bängen.
It doesn't matter what I use for anything.
Most large caravans are 2.35 so I'm really wide,
But I have no problems whatsoever with that bit.
I think that is almost more of a challenge and a little fun.
Try to try in with all the small villages with this wide.
However, what I find difficult for is the height.
Is happy something when it comes to height.
Total height is 3.42 centimeters and I've been under a couple of bridges
which is 3.50.
It's not funny.
I crawl.
I also have all the solar panels with glass outside which is the highest peak.
And looks 30 miles and stays for a few days.
It's actually smaller than I thought it would be.
The ramp at the back.
Did you do anything about it?
No, it's the same.
You get used to it.
It sounds pretty much to fold up/down it,
But I cared for about two weeks.
After that, I totally shit.
There are so much barking dogs and children who scream and so on.
It may let me too, but it has learned during the trip
That I went away with the intention to be stealth and be secret.
So I have a little too little capacity on it, but the principle works
So it's no wonder.
Do you still drink the water?
No not anymore.
I did it in the beginning, but of pure security or something.
When it has been several months and you do not know if there are bacteria
and so on.
So I use it to cook tea and cook pasta and all this.
The only thing I drink buy-water is pure drinking water.
Everything else I use for this.
And that's the same thing there.
When I have slide out on the wardrobe module
So I had a locking device on it.
But it is so insanely very load.
When running in the turns, the bracket has high up
and it has a lot of weight so that when the truck swings
So tolete the brackets at once.
So it was a simple but effective solution.
That's when I'm going somewhere, I'll push it in.
All the way in I lock it.
A temporary solution I made after 10-15 miles.
It has been sitting there ever since.
to threatened or insecure or insecure anything.
So the opportunity to close again and close around has done
That I am completely relaxed all the time.
Wherever I have stood.
Before this trip I had the same old bike
For 15-20 years something and during this trip I have grazed four bikes.
Huh!?
Yes...
I have become a bikeoman on the coup.
I bought an electric bike and it was very nice.
I had to use it three times before it was stolen down in Halmstad.
I didn't get far.
There are a lot of pensioners who have sold their house in Sweden.
Have any small cabin left or something in a forest glade,
sold his house, buying a camper and they spend
6, 8, 10 months down in southern Europe where it is warm and comfortable
It is by far the most common.
Then we have another group that is digital nomads.
Very many people who work out on the move.
Has it been expensive?
No, especially not this year.
When you hear friends and acquaintances complaining of electricity bills and food prices
And other things you feel very privileged.
One Tuesday afternoon when it is raining and you are fixing the laundry.
Without all the time I am in new places and I do not like the selfish focus.
I have taken a break, but it is definitely not dead.
I have one...
I have an upcoming project that will do
That I will resume Youtube again.
Then we have to say back!
We'll do that!
Have a nice day!
Hello to you!